



Eric Lempe Perin

Date of birth: 09/04/1994 | **Nationality:** Brazilian | **Phone number:**

(+55) 27992373693 (Mobile) | Email address: dev.ericlp@gmail.com | LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/eric-lempê-perin-4947b1191/

Address: Street ten, number 25, 29105100, Vila Velha, Brazil (Home)

ABOUT ME

I am a software developer with almost 7 years of experience in the area of I.T. I have a degree in information systems in Brazil. In this period I worked on several projects of diversified branches and acted as a full stack developer. I am organized, dedicated, studious, I like to learn and share knowledge. Always in search of improving and optimizing processes.

In May/2024 I will realize a dream of doing an exchange to study English in Ireland and I am looking for my first international opportunity

WORK EXPERIENCE

27/02/2021 - CURRENT Vitória, Brazil

SOFTWARE ENGINEER MINDTEC

I am responsible for technical and customer documentation, development, testing and maintenance of systems, and assist in the review of code of junior developers.

- Backend Developer;
- · Frontend Developer;
- Mobile Developer;
- · Database modeling;
- Development of automations Web and Desktop;
- · Development of integrations;
- · Support in bug fixes in the system;
- Developer Code Review:
- Development of technical and customer documentation;

28/07/2019 - 24/02/2021 Vitória, Brazil

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER PHARMANEXO

I was responsible for the development, tests and maintenance of the web system and integrations with product portals and suppliers.

- Database modeling with Mysql, PostgreSQL;
- · Backend development with PHP Codeigniter;
- Frontend development;
- Development of integrations;

27/11/2017 – 17/12/2019 Vila Velha, Brazil

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER ESC - ENGINEERING IN CENTRALIZED SOLUTIONS

As an intern, I participated in several web systems projects from different areas, working in the development, testing and maintenance.

- · Database modeling with Mysql;
- · Backend development with PHP Laravel;
- Frontend development with JS.

ICT HELP DESK AGENT COURT OF AUDITORS OF THE STATE OF ESPÍRITO SANTO - TCEES

As an intern, I helped in the support and implementation of the systems

- Monitoring in the execution of systems implementation;
- Configuration of computerized systems;
- Guidelines related to systems;
- · Monitoring in automation and project management;
- Installation and configuration of information technology equipment;
- Support in the administrative activities of the information technology sector.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/08/2015 - 01/08/2019 Vitoria, Brazil

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION SYSTEMS Faesa

Website https://www.faesa.br/

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **PORTUGUESE**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	A2	B2	A2	A2	A2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

CSS | PHP | Javascript | Laravel | MySQL | JSON | Git | PHP Codelgniter | Bootstrap | JQuery | SQL | RPA | Flutter | PostgreSQL | VueJS | TailwindCSS | TallStack | NodeJS | NestJS | Docker | Vuetify | TypeScript | REST API management